<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News and Views on Ammon Perkes personal webpage</title>
    <link>https://aperkes.github.io/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in News and Views on Ammon Perkes personal webpage</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Site via Hugo. Theme: Airspace, copyright &amp;copy; 2020 [Themefisher](https://themefisher.com) All Rights Reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 11:15:10 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://aperkes.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>3 years of Science in 6 minutes</title>
      <link>https://aperkes.github.io/blog/blog-post-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 11:15:10 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://aperkes.github.io/blog/blog-post-3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Back in July, I got to present at the Animal Behavior Society (ABS) virtual conference.&#xA;ABS is always a bit intense, not because the people are mean or intimidating,&#xA;I feel like ABS is one of the most welcoming conferences I&amp;rsquo;ve participated in.&#xA;It&amp;rsquo;s just so much. Most of the talks are 15-30 minutes, and they have about 4 parallel sessions going at once,&#xA;So you spend all day, for several days, running around the venue trying to get to the talks that you want to catch,&#xA;and inevitably you are faced with some impossible dilemmas and you just have to choose.&#xA;A friend of mine described it as a &amp;ldquo;science bender&amp;rdquo;, which I think is pretty accurate.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploration is for suckers</title>
      <link>https://aperkes.github.io/blog/blog-post-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2020 12:15:10 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://aperkes.github.io/blog/blog-post-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I love exploration. When I was a kid, I spent most of my time wandering around the roads and woods near my house.&#xA;I would leave after school on my bike and or roller blades and try to find roads parts of my neighborhood I&amp;rsquo;d never seen,&#xA;or I would walk along the creek that ran though my backyard all the way to where it met the Pearl River.&#xA;I still am always hoping to find new ways to get from place to place in Philly. Exploration is the best.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blogging from the command line</title>
      <link>https://aperkes.github.io/blog/blog-post-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 19:52:10 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://aperkes.github.io/blog/blog-post-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When I was 13 or so, I started a Livejournal. I don&amp;rsquo;t remember who got me into Livejournal,&#xA;but I spent hours writing updates, working on my background, color scheme, and profile pics.&#xA;(I think if you had the unpaid version you got a total of three profile picture slots. Memory was&#xA;pretty sparse back then it seems.)&#xA;When facebook came around, I gradually transitioned over. (I remember feeling strongly about the fact&#xA;that facebook was stupid and would never catch on.)&#xA;Like all of us, as Facebook got bigger, I stopped updating by livejournal, or the blogger that replaced it.&#xA;And then I moved to Twitter. Oh, and then I got married, and I had someone to talk to,&#xA;so I didn&amp;rsquo;t have this compulsion to write down all my thoughts on a carefully designed page.&#xA;So this all feels like a return to form, albeit 18 years later.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
